DONNY PHAN

Full Stack Web Developer

CONTACT

donthephan@gmail.com

4 647-818-2780

Toronto, ON

in donnyphanmeceng

donthephan

EDUCATION

University of Toronto

Sep 2004 to May 2008

Degree

BASc Mechanical Engineering

Lighthouse Labs

Nov 2021 to Feb 2022 Diploma Full Stack Web Development

Academind

Jun 2021 to Aug 2021 Certificate React

The App Brewery

Nov 2020 to Mar 2021 Certificate Computer Programming in Python

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

Material UI

REST API

CI/CD

Git & GitHub

MongoDB

HTML & CSS

NodeJS

Express

SQL & PostgreSQL

Unit Testing

Mocha & Chai

Jest

Cypress

Project Management

SUMMARY

A Full-Stack Web Developer with 9 years of experience in Mechanical Design and Project Management. Experience with PERN Stack - Front End in React, HTML, CSS & JavaScript, and Back End in Node.js, Express & PostgreSQL.

My Porfolio: www.donthephan.com

NOTABLE PROJECTS

StoryTime

TECH USED: React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Tailwind CSS, Daisy UI, Git/GitHub, Socket.io, RESTful API, Netlify, Heroku, Figma and Trello.

- App connects readers with people who want to be read to.
- Team project using Agile practices with daily scrum meetings.
- Responsible for Wireframing, Front End Design and Implementation, Webchat and Web Hosting.

Interview Scheduler

TECH USED: React, Storybook, Cypress, Jest, API and Git/GitHub.

- o Books, cancels and makes changes to interview bookings.
- Unit Testing.

E-Commerse Store

TECH USED: React, Material UI, Firebase and Git/GitHub.

- Interface connects to Paypal.
- Responsive Design.

Web Sudoku Solver

TECH USED: JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase and Git/GitHub.

o Solves from inputs through use of a recursive algorithm.

EMPLOYMENT

Diamond Marketing, Gotta be Candy

Aug 2022 to Present

Brand Ambassador

 Building awareness of marketing products with customers, improving the brand's visibility and customer loyalty.

Spec Furniture

Jul 2016 to Jun 2020

Mechanical Designer

- Initiated and scripted drawing tools to reduce design times, up to 90% reduction (60 min to 5 min).
- Trained new Designers to use AutoCAD, SolidEdge, and understand furniture industry standards.
- Consulted clients, helping them understand their needs while mitigating issues in design/production.

Array Marketing

May 2013 to Jul 2016

Project Manager Assistant

 Managed 2-3 teams of 4-5 members each, developing, producing and delivering Cosmetic Displays to 400+ stores world wide.